https://www.hooksandlattice.com/about-us#privacy-policy

Size
24"
30"
36"
48"
60"
72"
WINDOW BOX BUYING GUIDE
Read More...
LAGUNA CLEAT MOUNT
Read More...
OUTDOOR PLANTERS BUYING GUIDE
Read More...
PRE-POPULATED HANGING BASKETS
See More...
WINDOW BOX ARTIFICIAL FLOWER ARRANGEMENTS
Read More...
ARTIFICIAL FLOWERING PLANTS
Read More...
EXTERIOR SHUTTER BUYING GUIDE
Read More...
HOW TO MEASURE FOR EXTERIOR SHUTTERS
Read More...
FAUX BALCONY BUYING GUIDE
Read More...
WINDOW ACCENTS
Read More...
TERRARIUMS
Read More...
WALL SCONCES
Read More...
OUTDOOR LIGHTING FAQ
Read More...
Window BoxesShop all
Composite Window BoxesCopper Window BoxesFiberglass Window BoxesVinyl Window BoxesGalvanized Window BoxesWood Window BoxesWrought Iron Window Boxes
Pots & PlantersShop all
Hanging BasketsIndoor PlantersLarge PlantersPlanter AccessoriesRailing PlantersSelf-WateringSmall Space
Artificial PlantsExterior ShuttersIron AccentsIndoor AccentsOutdoor Accents
Account
Home
Hooks & Lattice
About Us
About Hooks & LatticeCan do curb appeal begins online at Hooks and Lattice. We are a window box, planter and exterior shutter manufacturer, supplier and retailer located in Carlsbad, California just north of San Diego. Since 2001, we have served retail customers and wholesale garden centers nationwide, offering top quality home and garden products that improve both indoor and outdoor living spaces.
If you have questions or concerns about our website, or would like more information on adding our products to your next "can do curb appeal" project, please contact us via our Website or call 800-896-0978. Our dedicated home and garden representatives are available from 7:00am - 5:00pm, Pacific Time, Mon-Fri.
Hooks and
Lattice
6056 Corte Del Cedro
Carlsbad, CA 92011
Tel: 800.896.0978 or 760-707-5380
Fax: 760.603.0862
Hours 7:00am - 5:00pm, Pacific Time, Mon-Fri
CONTACT USOUR RETURN POLICY
Your satisfaction is very important to us! All standard items are returnable for a full refund of the purchase price (outbound shipping charges will not be refunded), provided you contact us within 15 days of the receipt of your item(s). In order to be eligible for return, items must be unused and in the original packaging. Prior to making a return, please call toll free to secure a Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) from Hooks and Lattice. No refund can be issued without an RMA.
Made to Order Items: Items ordered in custom styles, sizes or colors are not returnable. Other items that are non-returnable once they have gone into production or shipped include: iron faux balconies, composite planters, PlanterWell Reservoirs that have chambers linked to each other, worm castings, worm tea and other perishable fertilizer items.
Exterior Window Shutters: ONLY ITEMS MARKED AS “QUICK-SHIP” are eligible for return with a 25% re-stocking fee (minimum of $25).  All other shutter items are considered a custom size and are not eligible for return.
Return Shipping Charges: Hooks and Lattice will cover shipping costs if the return is a result of our error in packing. In all other instances, customers are responsible for return shipping charges.
Damage During Transit: Damage must be reported within 5 days of receipt of the item (calculated according to the carrier tracking number based on date of delivery). We must report carrier damage claims immediately. In the event of damage during shipping, we require photographs of the affected items and any damage to the shipping container. Our carrier also requires that the box damaged in transit be saved and sent back by the customer.
If you are unsure whether an item is eligible for return please call us before placing an order. We have agents available from 7:00am - 5:00pm, Pacific Time, Mon - Fri.
ONLINE ORDER SECURITY
To protect our customers, all online transactions paid for via credit card and PayPal are handled with industry-standard SSL encryption. This ensures the highest level of security for all purchases made on the Hooks and Lattice website.
SHIPPING INFORMATION
We make every effort to ship your order as quickly as possible, usually within 2-3 days if an item is in stock and 2 to 3 weeks if the product is custom made. We ship to the continental US only. Additional fees will apply to ship to Hawaii and Alaska, contact us at 800-896-0978 for details.
Our shipping is via UPS FOB San Diego, California.
View Shipping Map »
CANADA & INTERNATIONAL ORDERS
Please call us to determine proper shipping and exporting costs. 800.896.0978
PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Hooks & Lattice collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.hooksandlattice.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Hooks & Lattice.com.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the siteplace an ordersubscribe to the newsletter and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information,
Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Hooks & Lattice collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To improve our Site
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To process transactions
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
To send periodic emails
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Changes to this privacy policy
Hooks and Lattice has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Hooks & Lattice
6056 Corte Del Cedro Carlsbad, CA 92011
Call Toll Free: 1-800-896-0978
sales@hooksandlattice.com
Testimonials
About Hooks & Lattice
Hooks and Lattice is a WONDERFUL company!!! One of the most important attributes of a good company is SERVICE. My purchase from Hooks and Lattice was so easy and without flaw. Everything about the transaction was terrific! After receiving the merchandise, I had a question and got the email answer within hours. The best part of the sale is the window box I bought is very, very high quality and BEAUTIFUL!! THANK YOU Hooks and Lattice!!
-- Sheree Rensel
Great Service
I search and evaluate product offerings and availability extensively before I buy. Hooks & Lattice offers a good variety. When I placed my order, it was acknowledged promptly and I received an e-mail notice telling me when it was shipped. It arrived at my house quickly and just in time for installation as part of a weekend project. I am very pleased with the company and the products I purchased.
Copyright © 2020 HooksandLattice.com, all rights reserved. | 800-896-0978
